Contact

amir_alimadadi_63@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/amir-alimadadi-b419183a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

SQL Server ASP.NET Core React.js

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Germany (Limited Working)

Publications

Extended Persian Tokenizer System study based on morphological analysis

Predicting the PVT properties of Iran crude oil by Neural Network

Object recognition methods as preprocess of object counting in BAL medical images

Amir Alimadadi

Full Stack Developer Specializing in Erp | Software Project Manager | Data Engineer

Tehran, Tehran Province, Iran

Summary

I am a data and programming lover, with a fast-learning personality. With a rational mind, I always divide a huge problem into many micro problems and find a suitable solution for each one. I have valuable experience in developing, maintaining, and agile team coaching in enterprise software solutions (like ERP) in huge companies.

I also have done some international projects for Calgary University and Chicago Stock Exchange in the platforms of .Net (Core and MVC), SQL Server, and React js. You can find some of my projects on my GitHub

https://github.com/amiralimadadi

Experience

Freelance

Freelance Full Stack Developer January 2019 - Present (4 years 8 months) Canada

Carrying out international projects in the field of programming for Canadian institutions like Calgary university and Testpredikt.com.

RojinTaak Agro Industries Co.

14 years 7 months

Software Project Manager and Database Administrator February 2009 - Present (14 years 7 months)

Tehran Province, Iran

ERP project manager.

Design and develop new features for ERP software.

Analysis and administration of database with a huge amount of data.

Senior Software Engineer and Database Developer June 2011 - September 2018 (7 years 4 months)

Iran

Design and implementation of management information systems for industrial companies. The software involves automation of all activities in the company and contains subsystems like accounting, inventory, and ...

Design and administration of database are in the job responsibilities.

Junior Software Engineer February 2009 - May 2011 (2 years 4 months) Iran

Ghadir Charity Clinic and Hamedan Journalist Center Freelance Programmer January 2008 - December 2009 (2 years) Iran

Responsible for software development as a volunteer in some organizations such as charity clinics and free journalists' centers.

Education

Bu-Ali Sina University

Master of Engineering (M.Eng.), Artificial Intelligence · (2009 - 2012)

Arak University
Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng.), Computer Software
Engineering · (2003 - 2008)

Roshd